

Alla Nesterova

Experience

2015 — now

Chief accountant • Artificial Core

2014 — 2015

Chief accountant • Pershiy tsentr terapiyi ta mlkrohlrurgiyi oka

2012 - 2013

Accountant • KESZ

2011 - 2012

Accountant • Park Kino

+380 96 497-99-67





Education

Sumy State University

2008 — 2011

Faculty of Electronics and Informational Technologies

ACCA

2016

Diploma of International Financial Reporting

SkillUp

2019

Front-end development

Online resources

2018 — 2019

Codacademy, Stepik, ITDV, Prometheus, Hubr and others

Skills

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React/Redux

About

I started my career in finances. I'm diligent, reliable, responsible, friendly and always try to do more than is expected of me. That allowed me to occupy chief accountant position in the last two companies I worked for. My collaboration with the latest company led me to realization that I want to be a software engineer. I like when everything is in its place and works as expected. I like to automate processes. And be a valuable member of a team that works on an engaging goal. Thank you for taking your time reading this. Hope I'll meet you in person.